http://www.nurserysupplies.com/about/privacy

Skip to main content
About Us
Privacy Policy
NURSERYSUPPLIES.COM Privacy Policy
What information do we collect? At NURSERYSUPPLIES.COM, we are committed to protecting your privacy. When you visit our website, only 2 types of info is retained: Your website usage information, collected on an aggregate basis, as you and other visitors visit our website and any direct information provided to us by the user through the use of forms. We will not collect any personal information from you that you do not volunteer to give us. NURSERYSUPPLIES.COM does not and will not sell, share, or rent this information to 3rd parties for any purpose.
Cookies: Unlike many other websites, NURSERYSUPPLIES.COM does not transmit, collect, or use cookies to identify members using our website.
Third Parties: NURSERYSUPPLIES.COM may provide third parties with aggregate statistics about our website, traffic patterns, and related site information. This data reflects general site usage patterns gathered during hundreds of customer visits to our website each month. This aggregate information does not contain behavioral or identifying information about any individual member but as a group over that period of time. NURSERYSUPPLIES.COM may also provide log files and other databases of user information to third parties for analysis, so we may develop a better understanding of traffic patterns through our site and thus improve our site design and content to make your experience at our website more enjoyable and productive.
Third party links: Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Security: We use reasonable precautions to secure the personal information you disclose to us in your browsing behavior.
Consent: By using our website, you give NURSERYSUPPLIES.COM permission to collect information about the pages served to you as an anonymous user for the purpose of calculating aggregate site statistics. NURSERYSUPPLIES.COM may occasionally amend this policy.
Questions? If you wish to change any information you have given us, or have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us directly.
Stay in touch
Sign up for our monthly newsletter!
I Am:
I am a:CustomerGrowerNew CustomerStudent/ResearcherSupplier
State
State/Province
StateAlabamaAlaskaAmerican SamoaArizonaArkansasArmed Forces (Canada, Europe, Africa, or Middle EastArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces PacificCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFederate States of MicronesiaFloridaGeorgiaGuamHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarshall IslandsMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaNorthern Mariana IslandsOhioOklahomaOregonPalauPennsylvaniaPuerto RicoRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirgin IslandsVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingAlberta, CABritish Columbia, CALabrador, CAManitoba, CANew Brunswick, CANewfoundland, CANova Scotia, CANunavut, CANorth West Terr., CAOntario, CAPrince Edward Is., CAQuebec, CASaskatchewen, CAYukon, CA
Email:
